Now we are going to sew our bear body together.
First, I want to slice a hole in the back that we are going to use for the stuffing.
So take the back bear section this is the front bear section is the one that we embroider on.
The back bear section is plain and just fold it in half.
Slice about a inch into there.
So you have a two inch slice on the back and that is what we would use that hole for when we want to stuff the bear.
Now look for the outside of the fabric.
This fabric does have that inside and outside.
You want to put the bears together, the bear sections together.
With the outside facing each other so I have the inside of the bear facing on the outside.
They call this right side together.